# Chung, PeiYun (Lu)

<u>lu.pychung@gmail.com</u> +886 910 075 741

# **Objective**

My purpose of design is focused on creating great products that meaningfully impacts people's live. With the practical experiences in visual communication and interaction, my enthusiasm, creativity and skills drive me to further explore the area of data visualization, new user interfaces and interactions, and mobile social networks.

#### **Education**

## M.F.A. in Visual Design

#### National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan

Sept. 2013 - Jun.2016

Major in Visual Design with Highest Honors, within top two grades in the class twice. Grade: 92/100

Visual Semiology, Public Arts, Culture and Creation Lab — Advisor: Prof. Yi-hsun Lee

Thesis:

Semiology on The Little Prince — The study of semiology in the animation, The Little Prince (2010), analysis of visual style, cultural meaning and integrated research of the previous publications.

#### **B.Des. in Visual Design**

# National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan

Sept. 2009 - Jun. 2013

Major in Visual Design *with Highest Honors*, within top two grades in the class five times. GPA 3.91/4.0 Final Year Project: Designed Ingenuity Exhibition, space design, animation video and publications.

## **Experience**

## **UX Designer & App Designer**

#### SHOPLINE Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2017 - Present

- Designed *Merchant App* interfaces and conducted prototype interaction testing, creating the customer service to 8,000 merchants approximately as one of the key contributors to the company and product.
- Prototyped new *POS* system and devised the user flow of the transaction process, product inventory and order management as the combo service product of ecommerce shop and in-store business.
- Reinvented *Admin* platform and storefront website with hi-fi prototypes on computers, tablets and mobiles, which is the major project to product teams increasing the profitability 120% in five months.
- Integrated *Design Guideline* consistent with the current corporate identity system, which is consisted with the parts created by the other three designers involved as the principle of product interface improvement.
- Customized PLUS website and prototyped new screens and interaction across multiple devices, which provides customer satisfaction to all 5 participants increasing the revenue over \$30,000 in ten months.

## **UI Desinger & Front-end Developer**

## Al Group Corp., Taipei

Oct. 2016 - Dec. 2016

- · Engineered front-end web design for the art museum big opening campaign with the architect institutions.
- Designed *JUP App* for the building and employee management of JUT Land Development Group., an architectural enterprise with approximately 100 people near the southwest city of Taipei.

# **UI Designer & Web Designer**

# Techgiant Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

- · Innovated the project Robelf visual identity and logo design, which primarily sustained the crowdfunding campaigns.
- Devised touchscreen interfaces and voice user interfaces with elegant high-fidelity prototypes both on the tablet and mobile for *Robelf* mechanic products, which raised roughly \$150,000 funds in one year on Indiegogo.
- Organized planning to Robelf web design from identifying solutions to prototyping validations, designing the related graphics such as production-timeline illustration and commercial photography.

#### Select Skills & Awards

Computer Vision & Graphics: VI Design, Data Visualization, Multimedia Design, Photography, 2D and 3D computation Design: User interface/experience design, interactive prototypes, Web design (native code, HTML/CSS/JavaScript)

Awards: Ingenuity (Vision Get Wild Award 2013), Pop-up Desire (DJP Co./HTC Packaging Awards, Silver Prize 2011)

Software: Sketch, Framer, Illustrator, Indesign, Photoshop, Premiere, After Effects, Autodesk Maya

Traditional Media: Pen/marker drawing, Pastel art, Watercolor, Acrylic painting, Oil painting